Guide to the Kenneth C.M. Sills: Administrative Records A01.02.08
George J. Mitchell Department of Special Collections & Archives, Bowdoin College Library, Brunswick, Maine 04011
- World War II Correspondence, 1940-1946, A01.02.08.13; 5.0 linear feet
  - Oliver, James C. (Bow 1917) (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Olson, Carl G. (Bow 1934) (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - O'Neill, Edward L. Jr. (Bow 1934) (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Orgera, Walter L. (Bow 1939) (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Orr, John E. (Bow 1940) (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Orth, William G. (Bow 1945) (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Oshry, Harold L. (Bow 1940) (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Paige, Milton C. (Bow 1944) (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Park, Thomas L. M. (Bow 1935) (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Parkhill, Charles L. D. (Bow 1946) (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Parsons, Edwin S. (Bow 1928) (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Patrick, R. L. (Bow 1945) (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Patten, Millard H. Jr. (Bow 1943) (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Pearson, Karl M. (Bow 1926) (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Pearson, Phillip C. (Bow 1936) (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Pelletier, Robert (Bow 1944) (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Pennell, Robert M. Jr. (Bow 1940) (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Perkins, David (Bow 1932) (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Perry, William H. (Bow 1933) (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Pettegrave, James P. (Bow 1930) (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Philbrick, Donald L. (Bow 1944) (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Phillips, Richard B. (Bow 1924) (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Phillips, Robert T. (Bow 1924) (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Philoon, Wallace K. Jr. (Bow 1945) (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Picken, Marshall W. (Bow 1943) (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Pierce, Benjamin (Bow 1943) (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Pierce, William C. (Bow 1943) (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Pike, Carleton M. (Bow 1917) (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Pillsbury, Alfred P. (Bow 1944) (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Pillsbury, Orin C. (Bow 1943) (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Pines, Harold L. (Bow 1941) (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Piper, Winthrop W. (Bow 1943) (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Pletts, Arthur M. (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Plimpton, John (Bow 1943) (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Poland, Lloyd L. (Bow 1939) (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Pope, Everett P. (Bow 1941) (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Porteous, L. Robert (Bow 1946) (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Porter, Robert (Bow 1937) (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Porter, Robert W. (Bow 1942) (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Potter, Gordon L. (Bow 1939) (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Presnell, John F. (Bow 1936) (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Prosser, Albert L. (Bow 1918) (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Qua, Robert F. (Bow 1943), Alan M. (Bow 1944), & Richard M. (Bow 1946) (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Randall (Bow 1946) (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Ray, Roger B. (Bow 1929) (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Reddy, Anthony N. (Bow 1945) (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Reed, George R. (Bow 1926) (Box 7, Folder 813)
  - Rehder, Gerhard O. (Bow 1931) (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Requa, Philip E. (Bow 1943) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Rice, William H. (Bow 1938) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Rich, John H. (Bow 1939) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Richards, Norman B. (Bow 1945) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Richardson, Edward T. (Bow 1943) (Box 8, Folder 4a)
  - Richardson, Henry W. (Bow 1933) (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Riley, John W. (Bow 1930) (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Rimer, Irving I. (Bow 1943) (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Ringer, Val W. (Bow 1942) (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Robb, Theodore D. (Bow 1943) (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Robbins, John A. (Bow 1941) (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Roberts, Brenton (Bow 1929) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Robertson, John R. (Bow 1929) (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Robinson, Richard E. (Bow 1946) (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Robinson, Samuel A. (Bow 1945) (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Rodgers, Allan (Bow 1931) (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Rodgers, John B. (Bow 1941) (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Rohr, Robert E. (Bow 1937) (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Rolfe, Andrew (Bow 1935) (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Roper, John C. (Bow 1932) (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Rosenberg, Wolfgang H. (Bow 1946) (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Ross, Philmore (Bow 1943) (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Rousseau, Laurier G. (Bow 1932) (Box 8, Folder 21a)
  - Rowell, Gordon A. (1935) (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Rudy, Robert R. (Bow 1946) (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Russell, Francis (Bow 1943) (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Ruth, Sherman B. (Bow 1943) (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Ryan, Donald J. (Bow 1944) (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Ryan, John F. (Bow 1944) (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Saba, Theodore R. (Bow 1942) (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Sabasteansky, F. F. (Bow 1941) (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Sammis, Donald L. (Bow 1940) (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Sandler, Maynard (Bow 1939) (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Saville, Richard L. (Bow 1944) (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Sawyer, Herbert H. (Bow 1945) (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Sawyer, Ronald (Bow 1945) (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Scales, L. Damon (Bow 1940) (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Schaffner, John B. (Bow 1935) (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Schenck, Frank X. (Bow 1946) (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Schlosberg, Richard T. (Bow 1918) (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Schoning, John B. (Bow ch 1946) (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Schonland, Robert R. (Bow 1947) (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Schubert, Kenneth M. (Bow 1947) (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Seagrave, Norman P. (Bow 1937) (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Sears, Donald A. (Bow 1944) (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Chandler (Seigal), Harold L. (Bow 1934) (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Semmes, J. Gibson (Bow 1945) (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Sewall, Edgar K. (Bow 1926) (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Shaffner, John E. (Bow 1945) (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Sharp, Richard W. (Bow 1938) (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Shaw, Hubert S. (Bow 1936) (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Shea, Alfred D. (Bow 1942) (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Shepard, Amos (Bow 1940) (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Sherman, Leonard (Bow 1944) (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Shipman, Robert O. (Bow 1944) (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Shorey, Henry A. III (Bow 1941) (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Shute, Benjamin R. (Bow 1931) (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Shute, John V. (Bow 1936) (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Shwartz, Harry M. (Bow 1919) (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Sigel, Franz (Bow 1931) (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Simmons, Cyril H. (Bow 1926) (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Simonton, William K. (Bow 1943) (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Singer, Joseph L. (Bow 1933) (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Skillings, Neal T. (Bow 1934) (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Slayton, Philip L. (Bow 1944) (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Slocum, Walter L. (Bow 1938) (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Smales, Robert T. (Bow 1946) (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Small, Cloyd E. (Bow 1920) (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Small, Harold M. (Bow 1946) (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Small, Stuart G. P. (Bow 1938) (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Smith, Alden G. (Bow 1925) (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Smith, Frank A., Jr. (Bow 1942) (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Smith, Frederick T. (Bow 1944) (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Smith, George E. (Bow 1945) (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Smith, Jacob (Bow 1931) (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Smith, Lacey B. (Bow 1944) (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Smith, Lendall A. (Bow 1931) (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Smith, Martin D. (Bow 1946) (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Smith, Philip A. (Bow 1929) (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Smith, Richard B. (ch 1945) (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Smith, Robert N. (Bow 1938) (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Smith, Thaddeus L. (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Snow, David R. (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Southard, Frank E. (Bow 1936) (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Soules, H. Kennedy (Bow 1942) (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Spear, Frederick A. (Bow 1945) (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Spencer, Jack (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Sperry, Robert J. (Bow 1944) (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - Stafford, Peary D. (Bow 1942) (Box 8, Folder 87)
  - Stanley, E. Jon (Bow 1943) (Box 8, Folder 88)
  - Stanwood, Geoffrey R. (Bow 1938) (Box 8, Folder 89)
  - Stapleton, J. W. (Bow 1945) (Box 8, Folder 90)
  - Steer, Richard M. (Bow 1937) (Box 8, Folder 91)
  - Stepanion, Charles (Bow 1941) (Box 8, Folder 92)
  - Stephens, Page P. (Bow 1941) (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Stetson, Edwin F. (Bow 1941) (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Stevens, Albert M. (Bow 1946) (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Stevenson, Henry H. (Bow 1930) (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Strandburg, Lewis A. (Bow 1943) (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Stratton, Arthur M. (Bow 1935) (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Stroud, Richard H. (Bow 1939) (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Stuart, Robert S. (Bow 1944) (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Sturtevant, Joseph E. (Bow ch 1943) (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Sulis, Ralph N. (Bow ch 1945) (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Sullivan, ---- (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Sullivan, Kenneth P. T. (Bow 1939) (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Sullivan, Richard W., Jr. (Bow 1940) (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Summers, Henry G. (Bow 1939) (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Sumner, Stanley (Bow 1943) (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Sumner, Thurston B. (Bow 1944) (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Sumner, Warren E. (Bow 1938) (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Swallow, George N. (Bow 1943) (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Swan, Frank H., Jr. (Bow 1936) (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Swan, Marshall (Bow 1929) (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Sweeney, Arthur (Bow 1945) (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Sweeney, Leroy E. (Bow 1945) (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Talbot, Harold D. (Bow 1940) (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Talcott, William L. (Bow 1945) (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Tarbox, James O. (Bow 1914) (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Taylor, G. P. (Bow 1943) (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Taylor, Harlan D. (Bow 1943) (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Taylor, Horace B. (Bow 1943) (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Taylor, Walter G. (Bow 1941) (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Tennyson, Leonard B. (Bow 1942) (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Terrill, Arthur A. (Bow ch 1946) (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Thomas, George R. (Bow 1941) (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Thomas, Harlan D. (Bow 1938) (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Thomas, Horace A. (Bow 1940) (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Thompson, Benjamin (Bow 1943) (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Thorndike, David (Bow 1946) (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Thorndike, Hubert (Bow 1944) (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Threfeld, Robert (Bow 1944) (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Thurston, Jason W., Jr. (Bow ?) (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Tolman, Albert W. (Bow 1925) (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Tonan, Mario A. (Bow 1942) (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Tonry, Herbert J. (Bow 1940) (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Tracy, James E. (Bow 1939) (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Trask, Burton W. (Bow 1927) (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Tukey, Philip E. (Bow 1939) (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Tukey, Richard E. (Bow 1940) (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Tuttle, Charles L. (Bow 1939) (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Tuttle, John A. (Bow 1944) (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Tyrrell, Robert L. (Bow ch 1943) (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Ulm, Donald S. (Bow 1943) (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Usher, William S. (Bow 1932) (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Vafiades, Lewis V. (Bow 1942) (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Vannah, Harold P., Jr. (Bow 1946) (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Van Soelen, Donald (Bow 1946) (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Van Valkenburg, Frederick A. (Bow 1944) (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Vergason, Edwin L. (Bow 1939) (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Wadleigh, Allyn K. (Bow 1938) (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Walker, Edwin G. (Bow 1936) (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Walker, John M. (Bow ch 1944) (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Walker, Leon V. (Bow 1932) (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Walker, Robert H. (Bow 1943) (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - -----, Wallace (?) (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Ward, Lawrence J. (Bow 1946) (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Warren, Francis (Bow 1919) (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Watt, Donald M. (Bow 1939) (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Watts, Alan O. (1940) (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Watts, Norman E. (Bow 1941) (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Webb, William (Bow 1938) (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Webster, Francis H. (Bow m 1911) (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Weeks, George W. (Bow 1928) (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Wehren, A. F. (Bow 1947) (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Weiner, M. L. (Bow 1945) (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Wentworth, John A., Jr. (Bow 1943) (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - West, James R. (Bow 1936) (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Weston, R. B. (Bow 1942) (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Wheeler, Caleb K. (Bow 1943) (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Wheeler, Paul LeB. (Bow 1940) (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Whitcomb, John, Jr. (Bow 1948) (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Whitcomb, Richard O. (Bow 1948) (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Whitman, Robert (Bow 1945) (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Whittenmore, Lawrence E. (Bow 1929) (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Wilder, Philip S. Sr. (Bow 1923) (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Wilder, Philip S., Jr. (Bow 1945) (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Wilder, Samuel B. (Bow 1943) (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - Will, Leonard F. (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Williams, John E. (Bow 1942) (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Williams, Richard J. M. (Bow 1946) (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Williams, Roger N. (Bow 1946) (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Williams, Stanley, Jr. (Bow 1937) (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Wilson, David C. (Bow 1946) (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Wilson, John H. (Bow 1941) (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Wilson, Paul H. (Bow 1938) (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Wilson, William (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Winer, Robert M. (Bow 1946) (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Wing, Carlton P. (Bow ch 1946) (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Wingate, Francis A. (Bow 1931) (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Winslow, Warren E. (Bow 1931) (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Woods, C. M. (Bow 1945) (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Woods, Joseph W. (Bow 1947) (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Woods, Robert H. (Bow 1940) (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Woodworth, Julian E. (Bow 1943) (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Wright, Joseph J. (Bow 1947) (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Wurts, Davis P. (Bow 1945) (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Wylie, Ralph H. (Bow 1939) (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Wyman, Willard G. (Bow ch 1920) (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Young, Clark (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Young, Philip C. (Bow 1940) (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Zwickler, William E. (Bow 1941) (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Lists and miscellany, including World War II casualty list (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Miscellany (Box 10, Folder 25)
- World War I Correspondence, 1917-1919, A01.02.08.14; 0.5 linear feet
  This series contains correspondence between Sills and Bowdoin men fighting in the war. Also included are correspondence with Bowdoin parents regarding the location of their sons and letters from military organizations providing information for prospective soldiers.
  - Correspondence: A-N (Box 1)
  - Correspondence: O-Z and Miscellaneous (Box 2)